Hello friends, welcome
to News24. Today we are going to talk
about the electric scooter. The
sale of the electric scooter is going to start from today.
All the information from Mi to finance is available.
Ola had
already announced the prices of these two electric scooters. The
ex-showroom price of the engine variant of the electric scooter is 99 thousand 999
rupees, while the ex-showroom price of the spin through variant is
1 lakh 29 thousand 999 rupees. So
friends, to get complete information about this,
watch this video till the end. Like,
subscribe and click
on the bell icon. So friends, let's start friends. Ola has
started the sale of its electric scooter S1 from today i.e. 8th September. The
day of 8th September has been chosen to start the sale of the MS Word scooter
because it
coincides with the eve of the day. The sale of the electric scooter has started with you. Ola
Electric launched its
Ola Ape One electric scooter
in the Indian market last month,
after which its sale was awaited. The
company will start the online sale of its Ola Ape One and Upvan
Pro electric scooters from 8th September 2021,
i.e. today.  Mi
Electric has
already announced the price of these two electric scooters. The
ex-showroom price of the Aishwarya end of the electric scooter is ₹99,999,
while the ex-showroom price of the X1 Pro Carrier is ₹
1,29,999. What will it be?
A statement issued by Mi Electric said
that the insurance for the Aishwarya end of the scooter will
start at ₹2,999 per month, while
for the Spinners, it will start at ₹3,199.
If you need financing, Mi
Financial Services has tied up with
leading banks, including Edifice Bank, HDFC Bank, and Tata Capital, to help you finance the Ola F1.
For insurance, buyers can
insure the scooter through the Ola and Ola app. The
company's insurance partner is
ICICI Lombard. Finance in a jiffy:
HDFC Bank will provide pre-approved insurance to
eligible customers within minutes. A
statement issued by Mi Electric
said that Tata Capital and
IDFC First Bank will process the digital KYC.
Eligible customers will be
given stand loan approval If you do
not need finance, you can make an advance payment of
Rs. 20,000 for Ola Aid One or Rs. 25,000 for Ola Aid One Pro
and pay the rest when we invite your scooter
Deliveries to start from next month
According to Electric Scooter
deliveries will start from October 2021
from this month The company will also provide test There
is also an option to cancel the order after cash variant
provided the scooter has
not been hidden for delivery from the factory
Range up to 181 km The S1 variant of the electric scooter
gives a range of up to 121 km on a single full charge while the F1 provides a range of
181 km on a single charge The
F-18 accelerates
from zero to 40 kmph in three point six seconds
while the F1
accelerates from zero to 40 kmph in three seconds So friends, if you
liked the information given in this video
and to get information from time to time, watch
this video
Like and share as much as possible, thank you